Nash, Al Audio-visual material /4188 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Al Nash Audio-visual material
1970-1985
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Nash, Al
/4188 AV
3.22 cubic feet
3.2 linear ft.
Audiovisual material.
8601289
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 12, 2014
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 04, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4188: Al Nash Additional Files
Nash, Al; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations
8601289
- Malcolm Young (Box 1)
- Songs (Box 2)
- G. Bowen Thomas - Nov. 17, 1978(?) (Box 3)
- Thesis - 8/11/1983 (Box 4)
- Bill Cook -- 10/14/1978 (Box 5)
- Paul Brodetsky - Nov. 1, 1978 (Box 6)
- Aug. 9, 1978 - (Box 7)
- COPES (Box 8)
- Do Not Use this tape (Box 9)
- Sept. 7, 1985 + Sept. 9, 1985 (Box 10)
- Geary (?) - (Box 11)
- Allen - 2/21/1980 (Box 12)
- Thomas Snyder - 10/20/1985 (Box 13)
- Robert Miller - 9/18/1978 (Box 14)
- Unlabeled (Box 15)
- Ed Coken - 7/21/1983 (Box 16)
- 9/18/1985 (Box 17)
- Unlabeled (Box 18)
- 9/5/1985 (Box 19)
- Eric Hoys -- 9/9/1978 (Box 20)
- 9/20/1978 (Box 21)
- Abramson - 2/20/1980 (Box 22)
- August 31, 1978 -- Dave Buckle (Box 23)
- CBS - July 21-22, 1970 (Box 24)
- TWU - 8/10/1983 (Box 25)
- 12/11/1983 (Box 26)
- April 29 (Box 27)
- Oct. 4, 1978 (Box 28)
- Oct. 29, Nov. 4, 1985 (Box 29)